allusefulinfo.com 2019-03-08

# Privacy Policy of AllUsefulInfo.com

Here at _[allusefulinfo.com](https://allusefulinfo.com/ "All Useful Info")_ , privacy of visitors is extremely important. That’s why we are publishing this Privacy Policy page to make all the visitors know about the important terms about our privacy.

This Privacy Policy page provides you the type of information we collect or receive at our blog and how these information are used.

### Log Files

Like many other websites, _www.allusefulinfo.com_ also uses log files. Our log files includes your IP Addresses, Internet Service Provider, Browser (User Agent), Date/Time Stamp, referring/exit pages, number of clicks to analyze trends, track users’ movement around the site, gather demographic information to better administer the website.

IP Addresses and other information we collect are not shared with anybody to be used personally, in fact we use such information to serve you better in terms of quality and security.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

**AllUsefulInfo**  makes use of cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences. We record user-specific information such as browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser to know on which pages users visit the most to customize Web Page content.

### Advertising Policies

  * [Google](https://allusefulinfo.com/tag/google/ "Google"), As a third part vendor uses DoubleClick DART Cookies to serve ads on **  allusefulinfo.com** and many other sites on the Internet
  * Users may opt out the use of DART Cookies by visiting Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy by visiting the URL:  https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some other Advertisement Partners may use cookies and Web Beacons. Our Advertising Partners are listed below:

  * Google Adsense
  * Media.net
  * Some other direct advertisers

These third-party Ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on  _allusefulinfo.com_ sends directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP Address when this occurs.

Other Technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third party ad networks to measure the effectiveness to their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. _allusefulinfo.com_ has no access/control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **All Useful Info’s  **privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Commenting Policy

Your comments to our site should be relevant to the content and should not contain bad or adult links. We have full rights to delete and edit any comment we find bad or vulgar without the permission of commenter. There are many reasons we delete or edit comments, such as:

  * Comments are made for promoting things on our site
  * Comments contain links to low quality or adult sites
  * Comments are not related to the content
  * Comments with lots of grammatical or typing mistakes

So, we’ve full rights to delete any comment we won’t find worth publishing.
